CALEB WELSH

Senior Software Engineer

INFO

ADDRESS

AZ, Tempe

PHONE

(480) 636-6823

EMAIL

c@khalieb.com

LINKS

calebwelsh.info

github.com/khalieb

SKILLS

Go

Bash / Ruby / Javascript

AWS

Linux

Docker

DASH/HLS

SQL

Git

Circle CI

Datadog

Fastly VCL

Memcached

PROFILE

My entire career has been working with smaller teams. This means you need to be ready to solve anything. If new infrastructure is needed, you stand it up. If there is a problem new to you, you research, design, and implement it. I like this. I believe it has made me well rounded and ready to take on any problem given to me.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Senior Software Engineer, Brightcove

Scottsdale, Az

Aug 2016 — Jun 2020

At Brightcove, I worked on Dynamic Delivery. This team's focus was every aspect of the VOD and SSAI pipeline. This included work with CDNs, HLS and DASH Manifests, Ad Tech (DFP, VAST, SmartXML), and TS and FMP4 Segment Delivery. Working mainly with Go and a handful of AWS Services (EC2, Dynamo, S3, etc).

Software Engineer, NuHome

Chandler, Az

Jan 2015 — Jul 2016

Built Public and Private APIs using Go, EC2, S3, and Dynamo to allow customers and clients link up.

Software Engineer, Protection Source

Tempe, Az

2010 — Dec 2014

Backend Web Development

Salesforce Development

Software Engineer (Intern), FOG Studios

Fredericton, NB

2008 - 2009

Web Development (Front and Backend)

EDUCATION

Computer Science, University of Advancing Technology

Tempe, Az

2007 - 2009

Computer Science, University of West Florida

Pensacola, FL

2004 - 2006